go go go go let's go sh it
上上上上上上上上上上上上上上
going don't climb up
走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走不爬上去
high a big and yummy
高高的,又大又美味的,
Burger my
我的汉堡汉堡
airplane watch
在我的飞机手表上做汉堡
out
外出
that was so scary little bison don't
外面那么吓人的小野牛
那是那么吓人的小野牛
that was so scary little bison don't
climb up high if you fall you might get
如此可怕的小野牛 如果你摔倒了 就不会爬高
如果你摔倒了,爬高点,你可能会得到
climb up high if you fall you might get
hurt I won't do that
如果你摔倒了,你可能会受伤 我不会那么做的
伤伤我不会那么做的
hurt I won't do that
again go home
我不会再那样了 回家去吧
回家回家 回家回家 回家回家回家 回家回家回家回家回家回家回家回家回家
again go home
now oh no oh no Sheriff Labrador someone
哦,不,不,不,没有警长拉布拉多某人
robbed my apartment what lead the way
哦,不,不,不,没有警长拉布拉多 拉布拉多 有人抢了我的公寓
please
请
what the thief did was terrible Doby
多比,那个小偷做的太可怕了
start
多比开始的时候 小偷做的事太可怕了
investigating oh
调查哦
no watch
无表无监视
out
外出
Footprints they must be the
脚印一定是
theves looks like the thief is good at
脚印一定就是那些脚印 看起来像小偷很擅长
贼好像很擅长偷贼
theves looks like the thief is good at
climbing the footprints lead that
看起来贼很擅长攀爬脚印
攀登脚脚足足迹导致
climbing the footprints lead that
way Sheriff Labrador look there's a
拉布拉多警长看起来
giant spider on the wall a giant spider
拉布拉多警长看起来 墙上有一只巨大的蜘蛛 一只巨大的蜘蛛
巨蜘蛛在墙上 巨蜘蛛在墙上
giant spider on the wall a giant spider
no that's the thief's shadow let's go
巨蜘蛛在墙上 巨蜘蛛在墙上 巨蜘蛛在墙上
不,那是贼的影子,我们走吧
no that's the thief's shadow let's go
yo ho yo
哟哟哟哟哟哟哟
ho what a
何 何 何 何 何 何 何 何 何 何 何 何 何 何
day oh they didn't close their
哦,他们没有关闭他们的
window
哦,他们没有关上窗户
ouch
触摸( A)
Go Daddy I'm going to bed good night
去吧 爸爸 我要睡了 晚安了
sweetie oh that was
哦,亲爱的哦
close Mr Wolf what are you doing
关闭狼先生 关闭狼先生 你做什么
there I'm enjoying the view Sheriff
关闭狼先生 你在那里做什么 我很喜欢看风景 警长
警长,我很喜欢这里的风景
there I'm enjoying the view Sheriff
Labrador said climbing up high is
我很喜欢拉布拉多警长说 攀登高处的风景
拉布拉多说爬高就是
Labrador said climbing up high is
dangerous
拉布拉多说爬高是危险的
危险
dangerous
oh what's that sound finally got in
危险啊,那声音终于响起什么了?
哦,那声音是什么 终于进入
oh what's that sound finally got in
you're a bad guy sweetie why aren't you
哦,那声音是什么 最终得到进入你是一个坏人 一个坏人,亲爱的,为什么你不
你是一个坏人,亲爱的,你为什么不呢?
you're a bad guy sweetie why aren't you
asleep daddy don't you dare say anything
你是个坏人 乖,宝贝,你为什么不睡着 爸爸,你敢说什么吗?
睡着的爸爸你什么都不敢说
asleep daddy don't you dare say anything
I'll sleep
睡着的爸爸,你敢说什么我都会睡的
我会睡着的
I'll sleep
now he's
现在他
gone this is
已经走了,这是
good oh that looks good too
不错哦,看起来也不错哦
Mr Buffalo I'm Sheriff Labrador open the
水牛先生 我是拉布拉多警长
door
水牛先生 我是拉布拉多警长 开门
门门
door
please oh what's going on we suspect a
门门,请,哦,发生什么事了 我们怀疑
拜托你,到底发生了什么 我们怀疑
please oh what's going on we suspect a
thief entered your house a
我们怀疑有贼闯进你家
贼贼进你家
thief entered your house a
thief
盗贼
ouch upstairs that's my son's
上楼的小偷,这是我儿子的
room
房间
swe
房间瑞瑞
瑞 瑞
swe
huh the thief escaped through the window
小偷从窗口逃走了
I'll get
小偷从窗口逃走了,我会得到
him
世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世 世
huh I got
他,我得到了,我得到了,
you
您 您 的 您 您
stop want to catch me you can
停下来想抓住我 你可以的
try oh no
别再想抓住我 你可以试试哦 不
试试哦不
try oh no
don't be afraid it's okay Doby let's
哦,不,不,不要害怕 没关系,多比,让我们
go
上去
stop oh watch
停止哦 看着
me stop it's
# 我停下来 # # # 我停下来 # # # 我停下来 # # # 我停下来 # # #
dangerous
我不要再说了,这很危险
危险
dangerous
oh
哦
no watch
无表无监视
me I'll never climb up high again you
我永远不会再爬上高高高的你
shouldn't steal things you're coming
我再也不爬高了,你不该偷东西
你不该偷东西来偷东西
shouldn't steal things you're coming
with
不应该偷东西 与你一起来
与
with
us Sheriff Labrador safety
我们拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids you shouldn't climb up high
说话的小孩,你不应该爬高
things if you slip and fall while
和孩子说话,你不应该爬 高的东西,如果你滑倒和跌倒
假若你滑倒,而坠落,
things if you slip and fall while
climbing you could seriously get hurt if
如果你在爬山时滑倒,你会严重受伤,如果
攀爬可能严重受伤,如果
climbing you could seriously get hurt if
you see other friends climbing up
如果你看到其他朋友爬上去 爬山就会严重受伤
你看到其他朋友爬上去
you see other friends climbing up
something you should stop them right
你看到其他朋友爬上一些东西 你应该阻止他们
有些东西你应该阻止他们
something you should stop them right
away or ask an adult for help please
有些东西你应该马上阻止他们 或者请大人帮忙
或向成年人求援,
away or ask an adult for help please
remember that w
或向成年人求助,请记住
记得
remember that w
the ghost
记得那个鬼魂
幽灵
the ghost
motorbike green
绿色摩托车
light stop at Red go at
红灯车绿灯停停 红灯停 红灯停 红灯停
Green
绿绿色
huh what's that there's no one driving
那为什么没人开车?
it
其 其 年 , 其 年 , 其 年 , 其
ow oh
呜哦
wo hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
你好 我是拉布拉多警长
Labrador I got hit by a ghost motorbike
你好 我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 我被一辆鬼摩托车撞了
拉布拉多 我被一辆幽灵摩托车击中
Labrador I got hit by a ghost motorbike
when I crossed the street just now what
拉布拉多拉布拉多 我被一辆幽灵摩托车撞了 当我过马路时
当我刚刚过马路的时候...
when I crossed the street just now what
a ghost motorbike we'll be right
当我刚刚穿过街过马路时 一辆幽灵摩托车会怎么样?
一辆鬼魂摩托车,我们会是正确的
a ghost motorbike we'll be right
there huh where is
何在 何在 何在 何在
he uh ah I'm
他现在在哪里啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊,啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
他啊,我,他啊,我,
he uh ah I'm
here that was
在这里,这是
close we're lucky to have hard
幸好我们很努力
scales Mr
幸好我们有硬秤
平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平 平
scales Mr
Pangolin you called the police right oh
潘戈林先生 你叫警察对吗?
潘戈林 你报警了哦
Pangolin you called the police right oh
yes I got hit by a motorbike running a
潘戈林,你叫警察对吗 哦,是的,我被一辆摩托车撞了
是的 我被一辆摩托车撞了 开着一辆
yes I got hit by a motorbike running a
red light and you know what there was no
我被一辆开着红灯的摩托车撞了 你知道没有
红红灯,你知道什么是没有的
red light and you know what there was no
driver it must have been a ghost
红红灯,你知道什么是没有司机的 一定是鬼魂
驱动器一定是鬼魂
driver it must have been a ghost
motorbike I'm so
司机一定是一辆鬼魂摩托车
摩托车 我是如此
motorbike I'm so
scared a ghost motorbike
摩托车 我好怕鬼魂摩托车
吓吓鬼魂摩托车
scared a ghost motorbike
I'm sure something's wrong here don't
被吓吓的鬼魂摩托车 我敢肯定这里出事了
我敢肯定这里有些不对劲
I'm sure something's wrong here don't
worry there's no case that I can't
我敢肯定这里出事了 不用担心 没有案子我不能办
solve now let's find the motorbike first
现在我们先找到摩托车吧
got
现在让我们先找到那辆摩托车
it every vehicle leaves a mark when it
每辆车都留下标记 当它
passes
每辆车经过时都留下印记
通行证
passes
by it's a
由它是一个
puddle
旁边是水坑
H H these are are cars tire
HH,这些是汽车轮胎
tracks and these are motorbikes tire
HH是汽车轮胎的车轨和摩托车轮胎
这些脚印是摩托车轮胎轮胎
tracks and these are motorbikes tire
tracks I found the clue it must have
这些是摩托车的轮胎的车轨 我找到了它一定有的线索
我找到了它一定有的线索
tracks I found the clue it must have
gone this
我找到了线索 一定是线索
把这个拿走了
gone this
way
往这边走
方形
way
woof let's
来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,来,
让我们
woof let's
go look over
过去看看
there
去那边看看
it can't be is it a real ghost there's
这不可能是真正的鬼魂
no such thing as a
这不可能是它是一个真正的鬼魂 没有这样的东西是
没有这样的事物,没有这样的事物,
no such thing as a
ghost there into the alley hurry
鬼魂在小巷里 匆匆赶来
up huh oh no it won't go far
哦,不,它不会走远
police Mr Turtle can you help us follow
警察,海龟先生 你能帮我们跟着吗?
the motorbike over
警察,海龟先生 你能帮我们跟着摩托车过去吗?
摩托车经过
the motorbike over
there
那边的摩托车
此处
there
Sure hold on
等一等,等一等
Mr Turtle are you sure you can catch
乌龟先生,你一定能抓到
it of
乌龟先生,你肯定能抓到它
年三月一日,
it of
course
课程课程
go let's
航程走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走走
go
上去
my bottom really
我的底部 真的
hurts where are
我的屁股真的很痛 在哪里
伤处
hurts where are
we
哪里有伤痛,我们在哪里
huh the go
转一转三转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转一转
motorbike
骑摩托车
摩托车
motorbike
huh
中、英、法、俄、西
stop
hhn 停止( 停止)
停止停止
stop
huh it's
{\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF
aele watch
这是Eele watch {\fn黑体\fs22\bord1\shad0\3aHBE\4aH00\fscx67\fscy66\2cHFFFFFF
outy
外部
I was really scared
我真的很害怕,我很害怕
chameleon you broke the traffic rules
我真的很害怕变色龙 你违反交通规则
你违反了交通规则
chameleon you broke the traffic rules
you're under
你违反交通规则 违反交通规则
下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,下,
you're under
arrest Sheriff labrador's safety
逮捕拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids traffic lights are the signals
儿童闲聊的交通灯是信号
to control traffic the red light means
聊天孩子的交通灯 是控制交通的信号 红灯意味着
控制红灯的交通
to control traffic the red light means
stop the green light means go
控制红灯 意味着停止绿灯 意味着离开
停止绿光意味着离开
stop the green light means go
and the yellow light means be careful
停止绿光意味着离开 黄光意味着要小心
黄光是谨慎的,
and the yellow light means be careful
whether you're a driver or a pedestrian
黄色灯光意味着要小心 无论是司机还是行人
无论是司机还是行人
whether you're a driver or a pedestrian
you should always follow the traffic
无论你是司机还是行人,你都应该一直跟着交通
您应该始终跟踪交通流量
you should always follow the traffic
lights if you don't you might get in a
如果你没有,你应该一直跟着 交通灯,如果你没有,你可能会得到一个
灯光,如果你不,你可能会得到
lights if you don't you might get in a
traffic accident please keep that in
灯光,如果你不,你会 发生交通事故 交通事故 请保持在
交通事故 请保留在
traffic accident please keep that in
mind laser pointers are not
激光指示器不是
toys the ball
玩具球的玩具
there it
在那里,它在那里,它在那里
is what's
是什么是
that it's a
它是一个
mon hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
你好 我是拉布拉多警长
Labrador there's a monster in the park
你好 我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多 公园里有个怪物
拉布拉多公园里有个怪物
Labrador there's a monster in the park
it's so scary please come right now a
拉布拉多公园里有个怪物 太吓人了 请马上过来
太可怕了,请马上来
it's so scary please come right now a
monster we'll be right
太可怕了,请马上来 做个怪物,我们做对了
怪物,我们就会是对的
monster we'll be right
there
怪物,我们马上就到
此处
there
Sheriff Labrador it's over there it's I
拉布拉多警长 就在那边 是我
was shining a beam of bright green light
拉布拉多警长,就在那边 我在闪耀着一束明亮的绿光
闪耀着一束明亮的绿光
was shining a beam of bright green light
it's so scary bright green light kids go
闪耀着一束亮绿光的光束 它是如此吓人 如此明亮绿光的孩子们离开
这么吓人,那么明亮绿灯 孩子们就走
it's so scary bright green light kids go
home now Toby let's go
好恐怖的绿光绿灯 孩子们回家去吧 托比 我们走
托比,现在回家,现在托比,我们走吧
home now Toby let's go
okay I'm not afraid of bright green
托比,我们走吧 我不怕亮绿色
我不怕绿绿明亮
okay I'm not afraid of bright green
lights anymore but I can't see
我不怕绿绿灯了 但我看不见了
灯光照亮了 但我看不见
lights anymore but I can't see
well ouch
灯光照亮了 但我看不清
OU the monsters got
怪兽的魔兽
me
怪兽抓着我
我,我,我
me
hey the
嘿,我嘿,我嘿
嘿,嘿,嘿,嘿
hey the
monster what
嘿怪兽什么
怪物什么
monster what
monster it's just a
怪物的怪物 它只是一个
怪物,它只是一个
monster it's just a
tree but I saw a beam of green light
怪物,这只是一棵树 但我看到一束绿光
树,我却看见一束绿光,
tree but I saw a beam of green light
shining over
但我看见一束绿光照耀着树上,
闪耀在
shining over
there
闪耀在那边
huh like
三、按种族、种族、族裔、族裔、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口、人口
this exactly just like that looks like
就像
和这个一模一样
this exactly just like that looks like
the green light came through the hole in
就像绿光从洞口穿进来一样
绿光从洞中穿入
the green light came through the hole in
the
绿光穿过洞口
排
the
tree there it is
那棵树,就是那棵树,
那里有树,有树,
tree there it is
again it's
再一次,它再次
gone something's in the
里面有东西不见了
push what's
推动
that it's just a
推什么推什么 它只是一个
它只是一个
that it's just a
pet I got it someone's using a laser
这只是个宠物,我得到了它 有人在用激光
宠物,我得到了它 有人使用激光
pet I got it someone's using a laser
pointer to play with their
我知道有人用激光指示器 来和他们的宠物玩
与他们玩游戏的指针
pointer to play with their
pets it's so bright it's so dangerous to
与宠物玩玩的指针 它是如此明亮 它是如此危险
宠物是如此明亮 它是如此危险
pets it's so bright it's so dangerous to
play with a laser pointer like that
宠物是如此明亮 它是如此危险 玩这样的激光指示器
用像这样的激光指针玩
play with a laser pointer like that
let's follow it then we'll find its
用像这样的激光指示器来玩,我们跟着它走,然后我们再找到它
我们跟着它走,然后找到它
let's follow it then we'll find its
owner that
拥有所有者
way watch
这样看的主人主
me I'm
我,我,我,我
stuck huh let's go that
来,我们走吧
way there you are come on here there
你从那里过来,过来
h y
在那里,你来到这里 在这里hyy
y ow my
哟,我的
eyes
看着我的眼睛
ouch a of Fire
火狱的烧灼,
right it's on fire over here
右边,这里着火了
too my tail
我的尾尾巴太紧
help
我的尾尾尾也帮了大忙
help Doby you need to hurry got
帮助多比 你需要快点得到
it
其 其 年 , 其 年 , 其 年 , 其
huh watch
CHCH 观察
out let's
出去,我们出去
go
上去
yeah pH
(pH) (pH)
H so it really was a laser
呵呵,pHH 所以它真的是一个激光
H,所以它真的是激光
H so it really was a laser
pointer wolf it's so dangerous to play
指尖狼 玩玩太危险了
with a laser pointer like that it's not
用激光指示器玩太危险了 就像它不是
用激光指示器 像这样的激光指示器 它不是
with a laser pointer like that it's not
a toy I won't play around with it
用激光指示器 像这样的激光指示器,它不是玩具,我不会玩它
again Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids laser pointers are very
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们激光指示器非常
儿童聊天 激光指示器非常
talk kids laser pointers are very
dangerous if they shine in your eyes
和小孩说话 激光指示器非常危险 如果它们照亮你的双眼
危险,如果它们照在你眼里
dangerous if they shine in your eyes
they can harm your eyes and even cause
如果它们闪耀在你的眼睛里,它们会伤害你的眼睛,甚至伤害你,甚至伤害你的眼睛,甚至伤害你的事业,那么它们就很危险。
他们能伤害你的眼睛,甚至能伤害你的眼睛,
they can harm your eyes and even cause
blindness also High powerered lasers can
他们可以伤害你的眼睛 甚至造成失明 高能激光器也可以
高能激光器
blindness also High powerered lasers can
burn things and cause big fires so don't
高能激光能烧东西,引起大火,所以不要
烧烧东西,引起大火 所以不要
burn things and cause big fires so don't
play around with them and be careful
烧东西,引起大火 所以不要和他们玩耍,要小心
与他们交接,而且宜於周密的游戏,
play around with them and be careful
when someone's using them please
和他们一起玩耍,当有人使用时要小心
当有人在使用它们时,请
when someone's using them please
remember
当有人在使用它们时 请记住
that no littering no
任何人不能抛下,不得抛下,
mosquitoes sh sh go
蚊子还早去
away so many
许许许多多的
mosquitoes help stop following
这么多蚊虫 帮助停止跟随
me oh no so many mosquitoes
哦,没有这么多蚊子
run what's going
运行正在运行的运行
on my head my lips my neck that's so
跑什么跑什么 在我的头上 在我的嘴唇 我的脖子
itchy what happened to you Sheriff
警长,你发生什么事了,好痒痒啊
Labrador mosquitoes are everywhere in
拉布拉多蚊子无处不在
到处都是拉布拉多蚊子
Labrador mosquitoes are everywhere in
town it's so scary look at what they did
镇上到处都是拉布拉多蚊子 看着他们做了什么太可怕了
镇镇太吓人了 看看他们做了什么
town it's so scary look at what they did
to us please help
镇镇太吓人了 看看他们对我们做了什么 请帮帮忙
请救救我们
to us please help
us they're
救救我们,救救我们,救救他们
coming Doby let's go take a
杜比,我们去吃一个
look got
杜比,我们去看看
看了看 看了看
look got
it
其 其 年 , 其 年 , 其 年 , 其
now they can't fight me Doby hurry up
现在他们打不过我了 多比,快点
okay more and more mosquitoes are coming
越来越多的蚊子来了
looks like their breeding ground is over
越来越多的蚊子来了 看起来他们的繁殖地结束了
看起来像他们的繁殖地 已经结束了
looks like their breeding ground is over
there oh let me check it
看起来他们的繁殖地在那边 哦 让我检查一下
out you can't fight
出不来,打不出来
me
我,我,我
my bottom ow my face help there are too
我的底部 呼呼我的脸 帮助有 也有
many of them
我的屁股,我的脸 帮助我的脸 有太多 他们太多
其中许多人,
many of them
go they're
他们中许多人去,他们
coming hide in the
隐藏在
Box oh that's so scary there are too
盒子哦,那太吓人了,有太可怕了
many of them what should we do papion
盒子哦,那太吓人了 太多人了,我们该怎么处理Papion
许多人中,有许多人中,有许多人中,有许多民族,有许多民族,他们中有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,他们中有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,他们中有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,他们中有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,他们中有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,有许多民族,
many of them what should we do papion
we're surrounded by mosquitoes we need
我们该做什么? 我们被蚊虫包围 我们需要的蚊虫。
我们周围都是蚊子 我们需要的蚊子
we're surrounded by mosquitoes we need
your help mosquitoes leave it to
我们被蚊子包围 我们需要你的帮助 蚊子离开它
帮助蚊子
your help mosquitoes leave it to
me poon always has a
你帮蚊子的帮助 留给我的便便 总是有一个
我总是有一个
me poon always has a
away
离开
p
离开 pp
wow papon why aren't they coming after
哇,爸爸,为什么他们不来找
you because I'm wearing mosquito patches
为什么他们不来抓你 因为我戴着蚊子贴
因为你因为我穿着蚊子贴
you because I'm wearing mosquito patches
and
因为你因为我穿着 蚊子补丁和
和
and
bracelets here you
手镯和手镯,
手镯在这里您
bracelets here you
go now they can't get close to me
走了,他们不能靠近我
hey look over there the mosquitoes are
他们现在走了 他们离我太近了 嘿 看看那边的蚊子们
嘿,看那边 蚊子是
hey look over there the mosquitoes are
coming from
看那边 蚊子从那边来
发自
coming from
there ew it
从那里起出,
在那里缝织着它
there ew it
stinks
在那里,它发臭
mosquitoes are still breeding they are
蚊子还在繁殖
most likely to breed in dirty and wet
蚊子仍然在繁殖,他们最有可能在肮脏和湿湿的繁殖中繁殖
最可能生长在肮脏和湿湿的品种中
most likely to breed in dirty and wet
places like this no wonder there were so
最有可能在肮脏湿湿的地方繁殖 难怪有这样的地方
难怪有这样的地方
places like this no wonder there were so
many mosquitoes in this
难怪这里有这么多蚊子
许多蚊子在此
many mosquitoes in this
town who on earth made this
这个城市里有许多蚊子,他们造在大地上。
大地上的居民,创造了这个城市,
town who on earth made this
mess oh
乱七七八糟哦
hey
乱七八糟哦,嘿嘿
嘿
hey
I'm not scared of
我不怕,我不怕
you how what's going on let's
怎么样的你 发生了什么事,让我们
go
怎么样的你 是怎么回事,我们走吧
上去
go
huh ouch
哈哈哈哈哈哈哈
ouch
呵呵,呵呵,呵呵,呵呵,呵呵, 呵呵,呵呵,呵呵,呵呵,呵呵,呵呵,呵呵,呵呵,呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵呵, 呵, 呵, 呵, 呵, 呵, 呵, 呵, 呵, 呵, 呵,
触摸( A)
ouch
help let's
来来来来来来来来 来来来来来来
go
上去
Pap watch
Pap 观察观察
me
帕帕看着我
I'm so
我是这么
sorry hurry
对不起对不起,快点
up
上上
hey Mr bison make sure to keep your
嘿,野牛先生 一定要保持你的
surroundings clean from now on I will
嘿 野牛先生 确保你周围的环境从现在开始保持清洁 我会的
从今以后干净的周围环境 我会的
surroundings clean from now on I will
and I'll never litter
从今以后干净的周围环境 我将永不丢弃
again Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids mosquitoes in summer are
夏日说闲话的蚊子是
annoying not only do they Bight but they
夏天的蚊子聊天的孩子 不仅很烦人 而且很烦人
不仅伤哉他们,而且伤他们,
annoying not only do they Bight but they
can also spread
他们不仅伤风害俗,而且能散布,
也可以传播
can also spread
diseases mosquitoes usually breed in
蚊子通常在
dirty and wet places so we need to keep
蚊子通常在肮脏和湿湿的地方繁殖,所以我们需要保持
肮脏湿湿的地方 所以我们需要保持
dirty and wet places so we need to keep
our houses
肮脏和潮湿的地方 所以我们需要 保持我们的房子
我们的房屋
our houses
clean also we need to keep our town
我们的房屋清净,我们也需要 保持我们的小镇
还要保持城市的干净
clean also we need to keep our town
clean and don't litter please remember
还要保持干净,还要保持城市干净,不要乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱乱
清干净净的,不要乱扔垃圾,请记住
clean and don't litter please remember
that little chick was taken by
不要乱丢垃圾,不要乱丢垃圾 请记住那个小妞被带走了
ants I'm so
蚂蚁我是如此
hungry why is the donut moving
为什么甜甜圈在动
hey why is everything
为什么每件事物都如此
moving wake brother ouch
正在搬家的兄弟抚摸
brother I still want to
我还是想
sleep ouch it hurts brother what's wrong
睡在睡着中 伤害兄弟什么是错的
my arm it
睡在睡着中 伤到兄弟 伤到我的手臂
hurts hi I'm Sheriff Labrador Sheriff
你好 我是拉布拉多警长
Labrador please help us my brother got
我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 请帮帮我弟弟
拉布拉多,请你帮帮忙,我哥哥
Labrador please help us my brother got
bitten by our picnic mat what bitten by
拉布拉多,请帮助我们 我的哥哥被咬 被我们的野餐垫
被我们的野餐垫咬 被什么咬 被什么咬 被什么咬
bitten by our picnic mat what bitten by
a picnic mat we'll be right
被野餐垫咬到 被野餐垫咬到 被野餐垫咬到
野餐的垫子,我们会是正对的
a picnic mat we'll be right
there
野餐垫子,我们马上就到
all the toys and snacks just moved by
所有的玩具和零食 刚刚移动的所有玩具和零食
themselves and then my brother got
所有的玩具和零零食 都由他们自己移动,然后我哥哥得到了
然后,我哥哥被我弟弟
themselves and then my brother got
bitten by the picnic match little chick
后来我弟弟被野餐比赛咬了 小妞
被野餐比赛咬到的小妞
bitten by the picnic match little chick
where did you get hurt here it hurts so
被野野餐比赛咬伤的小妞 在这里你受伤了
你在这里哪里受伤了 哪里受伤了 哪里受伤了 哪里受伤了
where did you get hurt here it hurts so
much so it's true picnic mat can run and
你在这里受伤了 伤的很重 所以野餐垫可以跑动
所以这是真正的野餐垫 可以运行和
much so it's true picnic mat can run and
bite
所以野餐的垫子可以跑着咬着咬着咬着咬着咬着
咬 咬 咬 咬
bite
people stop
人停止 人停止
huh huh it's just a normal picnic
只是普通野餐 只是普通野餐
mat watch out for the
只是个普通野餐垫子 注意看好
垫子当心
mat watch out for the
ant looks like little chick got bitten
蚂蚁看起来像小鸡被咬了
by an ant like this it looks venomous we
蚂蚁看起来像小小鸡 被蚂蚁咬 像这样 它看起来有毒,我们
这样的蚂蚁,在我们看来,是毒的,
by an ant like this it looks venomous we
need to take him to the
像这样的蚂蚁看起来有毒 我们必须带他去
需要带他去
need to take him to the
hospital h
需要送他去医院
医院h
hospital h
don't fight me
医院啊,别跟我打架啊
Ant brother
蚂哥
chick it went
小鸡,它去了
away so many ant hills and here
如此多的蚂蚁山和这里
too so
如此多的蚂蚁山和这里也如此
many oh no run
许许多多哦没有运行
they're
他们是
coming stop chasing
他们来了 停止追逐
us go
我们走,我们走,我们走
up you can't catch us
你追不上我们
now they're still following
现在他们仍然跟着
us
他们现在还跟着我们
hurry
快点
come
快点来
on now you can't follow us
现在你不能跟着我们了
huh seriously I can't believe
说真的,我真不敢相信
it they're
它们是
here there labador what do we do now I'm
这里的拉玛多拉玛多,我们现在该怎么办?
calling papion for
在那里,拉马多,我们该怎么办 现在,我叫Papion为
呼叫Papion的电话
calling papion for
support huh what's this ew it
呼papion 请求支持 哼,这是什么 ew it
stinks papum we're being chased by ants
我们被蚂蚁追赶
we need your help and oh I know what to
我们被蚂蚁追赶 我们需要你的帮助
и惠璶腊 и笵或快
we need your help and oh I know what to
do I'll be right
и惠璶腊 и笵赣或暗 и穦癸
我做的,我会做对的
do I'll be right
there
此处
this
这笔
way now you can't get
这样你现在就搞不到了
us uhoh we're getting shorter oh no
哦,我们越来越短了哦,哦,不,不
they're all around
哦,我们越来越短了 哦,不,他们周围都是
周围到处是他们
they're all around
us it's trying to fite my
都在我们周围 试图适应我
我们这帮人想用我的
us it's trying to fite my
bottom
我们这帮人想把我的屁股合合起来
puppy always has a way stay
小狗总是有办法留下来的
bom aren't those my
# 不是我的宝贝 # # # 不是我的宝贝 # # #
socks it's
这不是我的袜子
we're finally safe papion to the
我们终于安全了
hospital little chick needs to be
我们终于安全到医院了 小妞需要安全到医院
医院的小小鸡 应该是医院的小鸡
hospital little chick needs to be
treated got
医院的小鸡需要治疗 得到治疗
it Sheriff Labrador safety
拉布拉多安全警长
talk kids you shouldn't touch ants or
谈论孩子,你不应该触动蚂蚁或
get too close to their Hills some ants
闲谈小孩,你不应该碰蚂蚁 或太靠近他们的山丘,有些蚂蚁
离山太近了,有些蚂蚁
get too close to their Hills some ants
are venomous and if you get bitten by
有些蚂蚁有毒 如果你被咬到
毒害者,如果你们被咬,
are venomous and if you get bitten by
them it can swell up and even endanger
有毒,如果你被它们咬了, 它会膨胀,甚至危险
它们能膨胀,甚至危害,
them it can swell up and even endanger
your life please remember that
它可以膨胀甚至危及你的生命 请记住
W chew your
咀嚼你
food a long long time ago there was a
很久很久以前的很久以前 食物中就有一个
monster who loved to play hide and seek
很久很久以前 有个怪物喜欢玩捉迷藏
喜欢玩捉迷藏的怪物
monster who loved to play hide and seek
should eat slowly little
喜欢玩捉迷藏的怪物 应该慢慢吃一点
慢慢吃,慢慢吃,慢慢吃
should eat slowly little
hamster come on guys let's play Red
慢慢吃吧,小仓鼠 快来,伙计们,我们来玩红
仓鼠,来吧,伙计们,让我们玩红
hamster come on guys let's play Red
Light Green Light I'm coming oh oh wait
仓仓,来吧,伙计们 让我们玩红光绿灯 我来了哦哦,等等
绿灯,我来了哦哦哦等待
Light Green Light I'm coming oh oh wait
for
绿灯,我来了 哦,哦,等待
用于
for
me are you ready Green
格林,你准备好了吗?
Line someone laugh come out no it wasn't
有人笑一笑一笑的一行出来 不,不是的
us come and pl with
有人笑一笑一笑 不,不是我们一起来
我们一起来来来来去去
us come and pl with
me who's
我们一起来 和我一起 谁是
talking I'm coming for
说我要来找你
you it's so
我正要来找你,真的
scary the monster's chasing us
吓怕怪物追我们
huh Don't Be Afraid kids it's
吓怕怪物追着我们,别怕孩子
不要害怕孩子,这是
huh Don't Be Afraid kids it's
us what's going on there was an
孩子们别害怕 是我们
我们所经历的
us what's going on there was an
invisible monster and it told us to play
我们这里发生的事情 是一个看不见的怪物 它告诉我们玩
看不见的怪物 它告诉我们要玩
invisible monster and it told us to play
with it it was so
它告诉我们 玩它,它是如此
与它在一起是如此
with it it was so
scary oh an invisible monster it's right
与它是如此可怕 哦,一个看不见的怪物 这是对的
哦,一个看不见的怪物 这是对的
scary oh an invisible monster it's right
over there let's go have a
哦,一个看不见的怪物 它就在那边,我们去有一个
那边,我们去那边玩玩吧
over there let's go have a
look there's no invisible monster it's
你看,没有看不见的怪物 它,它
probably just hiding somewhere
你看,没有看不见的怪物 它可能只是躲在某处
可能只是躲藏在某处
probably just hiding somewhere
what's that
可能只是躲在某处 是什么
sound huh right
右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右 右
here go away
在这里走开吧
monster Mr Marmon I'm officer Doby not a
马门先生,我是多比警官
马蒙先生,我是多比警官
monster Mr Marmon I'm officer Doby not a
monster pH but I heard a strange sound
马蒙先生,我是多比警官 不是个怪物PH 但我听到一个奇怪的声音
怪兽PH 但我听到一个奇怪的声音
monster pH but I heard a strange sound
coming from the tent it was so scary
但我听到一个奇怪的声音 从帐篷里传来,它是如此可怕
从帐篷里出来,好吓人
coming from the tent it was so scary
that tent over there come on let's
帐篷从帐篷里出来,好吓人 那边的帐篷快来,我们来
那边的帐篷 来,我们来
that tent over there come on let's
go
那边的帐篷,快来,我们走吧
H why is this earphone on the
为什么这个耳机在
plate Don't Be Afraid guys Sheriff
为什么盘子上有这个耳机? 别怕,警长
别害怕,警长
plate Don't Be Afraid guys Sheriff
Labrador will catch the
别害怕 拉布拉多警长会抓住
拉布拉多将赶上
Labrador will catch the
monster you will find
拉布拉多会抓住你找到的怪物
你将发现
monster you will find
me I'm Hing
怪物,你会找到我 我是兴星
我,我,我,我,阿星
me I'm Hing
right the sound is coming from Little
小小的声音来自小小
右侧的声音来自小小
right the sound is coming from Little
hamster's
右侧的声音来自小仓鼠的声音
仓鼠的
hamster's
tummy
仓鼠的肚子
肚子
tummy
a how did it get into my
肚子怎么进到我肚子里了
tummy ow oh my
肚子啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
tummy Sheriff
我的肚子啊啊啊啊啊啊啊我的肚子 警长
牡
tummy Sheriff
Labrador the monster it's inside little
拉布拉多警长 怪物 它在小里面
拉布拉多 怪物 它在小里面
Labrador the monster it's inside little
hamster's tummy
拉布拉多 怪物 它在小仓鼠的肚子里
仓鼠的肚子
hamster's tummy
what I'm right here that's the monster's
仓鼠肚子,我在这里,这是怪物的
我在这里,这是怪物的
what I'm right here that's the monster's
voice don't be afraid the sound just
我在这里的,是怪物的声音 不必害怕声音的声音
声音不要害怕声音的声音
voice don't be afraid the sound just
came from the
声音不要害怕 声音刚刚来自
来自于
came from the
earphone little monkey is this
这只小猴子是从耳机里传来的 是这个吗?
小猴子,这只耳机
earphone little monkey is this
yours yes I put it on the table but
小猴子的耳机是你的 是的,我把它放在桌子上,但是...
是的,我把它放在桌子上,但是... ...
yours yes I put it on the table but
where's the other one H the earphone on
是的,我把它放在桌子上 但另一个耳机在哪?
另一只耳机在哪?
where's the other one H the earphone on
the plate and the monster's voice coming
另一只耳机在盘子上 怪兽的声音就来了
盘子和怪兽的声音来了
the plate and the monster's voice coming
from Little hamster's tummy I got it
盘子和怪兽的声音 来自于小仓鼠的肚子 我得到了它
从小仓鼠的肚子 我得到了它
from Little hamster's tummy I got it
little monkey's earphones fell on the
从小仓鼠的肚子 我得到了它 小猴子的耳机掉在
小猴子的耳机掉下来了
little monkey's earphones fell on the
plate and little hamster ate one of
小猴子的耳机掉到盘子上 小仓鼠吃了其中一只
和小仓鼠吃了一个
plate and little hamster ate one of
them that's why the sound was coming
小仓鼠吃掉其中一只 所以声音才传来
所以声音才会传来
them that's why the sound was coming
from his tummy oh I remember now little
这就是为什么声音来自他的肚子 哦,我记得现在很少
从他的肚子啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊啊
from his tummy oh I remember now little
hamster gobbled up the food and I told
我记得小仓鼠把食物 吞了起来,我告诉
仓鼠吞食食物,我告诉
hamster gobbled up the food and I told
him to take his time and chew his food
仓鼠吞食食物,我叫他慢慢吃 咀嚼食物
以便他抽时间吃食,而咀嚼他的食物;
him to take his time and chew his food
where is he now we need to take him to
现在他在哪里? 我们需要带他去
他现在在哪里 我们需要带他去
where is he now we need to take him to
the hospital he went that way Doby let's
他现在在哪里? 我们现在需要带他去医院 他往多比去的医院
go little hamster little hamster
小仓鼠小仓鼠小仓鼠
hamster it hurts so much please come out
仓仓,很痛,请出来
of my
仓仓,很痛,请从我身边出来
tummy watch out
小心肚子
ouch daddy
爱打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打 爸爸打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打打
look oh no the road is
哦,看,没有路的路是
blocked Doby leave it to
被封锁的多比让给
me
我,我,我
my tummy hurts so much little hamster
我的肚子好痛啊,小仓鼠
you've swallowed an earphone we'll take
我肚子好痛,小仓鼠 吞下耳机
你吞下了一个耳机 我们用它
you've swallowed an earphone we'll take
you to the hospital
你吞了个耳机 我们送你去医院
now Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长现在的安全
talk kids when you eat food you should
现在拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们,当你吃东西的时候,你应该吃
吃饭时跟小孩聊天,应该吃饭
talk kids when you eat food you should
chew it well don't gobble it up
吃饭的时候说说话的小孩吃东西,你应该好好嚼它,不要把它吸起来
咀嚼它好,不要把它吸起来
chew it well don't gobble it up
otherwise it might cause indigestion or
别把它嚼起来 否则可能会消化不良或消化不良
否则可能导致消化不良,或
otherwise it might cause indigestion or
you might accidentally swallow something
否则可能会导致消化不良 或者你可能会不小心吞下什么东西
你可能会不小心吞下什么东西
you might accidentally swallow something
that isn't food if that's the case let
你可能会不小心吞下一些不是食物的东西 如果是这样的话
如果是这样的话,那不是食物
that isn't food if that's the case let
an adult know and go to the hospital
如果情况是这样的话,那不是食物 让成年人知道,去医院
成年人知道就去医院
an adult know and go to the hospital
right away please remember
大人知道就立刻去医院,请记住
that never play with
永不与
caterpillars h a
毛毛虫 h a
caterpillar it looks
毛毛虫 长得像毛毛毛虫
它看起来像毛毛虫
caterpillar it looks
funny
滑滑
ouch
滑滑的抚摸
huh a
(a) 经济、社会、文化权利
caterpillar huh are they all scared of
毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛
caterpillars
毛毛虫
ouch
触摸( A)
OU Sheriff Labrador so many caterpillars
拉布拉多警长 这么多毛毛虫
are in there it's really
拉布拉多警长 这么多毛毛虫在里面 真的
里面真的有,真的有
are in there it's really
scary the
可怕的恐怖
caterpillar a let's
毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛
go over
过过去
there little little turtle are you
小乌龟,小小乌龟是你
okay I I'm so
小小乌龟,你没事吧,我好,我好
好了,我没事,我是如此
okay I I'm so
itchy it feels like something's under my
好痒好痒好痒 感觉好像有东西在我下面
感觉好像有东西在我下面
itchy it feels like something's under my
shell so itchy so itchy
感觉好像有东西在我外壳下 痒痒痒痒痒痒痒痒痒
another
另一个
caterpillar my
我的毛毛毛毛毛 我的毛毛毛 我的毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛
neck my nose oh no the caterpillars are
我的脖子 我的鼻子 哦 没有毛毛虫
venomous the treatment is all done
毒气 治疗已经全部完成
you'll feel better
毒气的治疗都做好了 你会感觉好些
你会感觉好一点的
you'll feel better
soon caterpillars usually live in the
很快你就会感觉好些了 毛毛虫通常住在
很快毛毛虫通常住在
soon caterpillars usually live in the
woods they won't leave there by the El
很快毛毛虫通常住在树林里 他们不会离开的
林林林,他们不会离开 在那里埃尔
woods they won't leave there by the El
unless someone moves them on
除非有人动起来 否则他们不会离开那里
除非有人移动它们
unless someone moves them on
purpose oh I
除非有人故意移动它们
目的 oh I
purpose oh I
remember when I was doing Tai Chi this
我还记得我做太极的时候
还记得我做太极的时候
remember when I was doing Tai Chi this
morning I saw Little Wolf catching
记得我早上在做太极日时 看见小狼捉到
早上我看见小野狼捕捉
morning I saw Little Wolf catching
caterpillars in the
早上我看见小野狼抓着毛毛虫
毛毛虫
caterpillars in the
bush Little Wolf must be scaring people
小狼一定吓到人了
with caterpillars we need to stop him
小狼一定用毛毛虫吓人 我们得阻止他
now it's so fun to scare people with
现在吓吓人们 感觉很好玩
caterpillars let's go my caterpillar
现在用毛毛虫吓吓人很好玩,走吧,我的毛毛虫
小毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛毛
caterpillars let's go my caterpillar
Army why is my arm so
为什么我的手臂是我的手臂
itchy it's getting
陆军为什么我的手臂这么痒 越来越痒
越来越痒了
itchy it's getting
worse oh no I'm itching all
越来越痒了 哦,不,我痒了所有
更糟糕的哦不,我痒痒所有
worse oh no I'm itching all
over C billar go go
更糟糕哦,不,我痒痒 全身在C一磅去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去去
away
离开
stay away from me
离我远点
help it's Little
离我远一点 帮帮忙 是小小
帮助是小
help it's Little
Wolf over there let's
帮帮忙,是小野狼那边,我们来
那边的野狼,我们到那边去
Wolf over there let's
go get off me so many
离开我这么多人
caterpillars
毛毛虫
the caterpillars are
毛毛虫是
everywhere be careful let's
毛毛虫无处不在 小心点,让我们
到处都小心,让我们
everywhere be careful let's
go
到处都小心点,我们走吧
上去
go
okay help help
帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助 帮助帮助 帮助帮助 帮助帮助 帮助帮助 帮助帮助 帮助帮助 帮助帮助 帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助 帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助帮助
me let's get out of here
и瞒秨硂
uh
и瞒秨硂ㄠ
uh hey
嗯嘿
hey aha I have an idea Super
嘿嘿嘿哈哈 我有个主意 超级
Tornado oh poor
" 旋风 " oh poor
kid I'll never catch caterpillars
龙卷风啊可怜的孩子 我永远抓不到毛毛虫
小子,我永远抓不到毛毛虫
kid I'll never catch caterpillars
again Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长的安全
talk kids some caterpillars and bugs are
拉布拉多警长的安全谈话 孩子们 一些毛毛虫和虫子
和孩子聊天 毛虫和虫虫
talk kids some caterpillars and bugs are
venomous if they bite you the spot might
有些毛虫和虫虫如果咬你 就会毒死你
如果他们咬你,就会毒死你
venomous if they bite you the spot might
get red swollen at itchy or even worse
如果他们咬你,毒气就会发作 发痒或更糟糕的红肿
皮肤痒或甚至更糟糕时 红发肿胀
get red swollen at itchy or even worse
remember not to touch them and never
在痒痒时红发肿,甚至更糟 记得不要碰他们,永远不要碰他们
不记念不记念,不触他们,永不记不记念,
remember not to touch them and never
play around with
绝不要记念他们,绝不要与他们交接,绝不要与他们交接,
玩玩玩玩玩玩玩玩
play around with
them also if a bug lands on you don't
如果有虫虫落在你身上,你也可以和它们一起玩耍。
如果有虫虫落在你身上,他们也是一样的;如果有虫虫落在你身上,你没有,
them also if a bug lands on you don't
just grab it with your hand gently
如果有虫虫落在你身上 也不要用手轻轻地抓住它
轻轻地用手抓住它
just grab it with your hand gently
remove it with
只要用手抓住它 轻轻地把它拿开 轻轻地把它拿开
删除它时
remove it with
tools please remember that
使用工具删除它, 请记住
工具请记住
tools please remember that
Little Koala is
请记住小Koala
小可乐是
Little Koala is
missing little duck little rabbit Little
小鸭子小兔子小
Koala
小鸭子小兔子小科阿拉
科阿拉
Koala
oh Little
呵哦小
Koala where is Little
小科阿拉 哪里是小
Koala,哪里是小小
Koala where is Little
Koala
科阿拉
it's so hot Doby you'll feel cooler if
Koala,它是如此热的多比,你会觉得更凉爽,如果
这么热的多比,你会觉得更凉爽,如果
it's so hot Doby you'll feel cooler if
you just
这么热多比,你会觉得更凉爽,如果你只是
只是你
you just
relax woof hi I'm Sheriff Labrador
放松点,嗨 我是拉布拉多警长
我是拉布拉多警长
relax woof hi I'm Sheriff Labrador
Sheriff Labrador this is Miss sheep at
我是拉布拉多警长 拉布拉多警长 这是羊小姐
拉布拉多警长,我是羊小姐
Sheriff Labrador this is Miss sheep at
the preschool my student Little Koala is
拉布拉多警长 这是在学前班的羊羊小姐 我的学生小考拉
我的学前班学生小考拉
the preschool my student Little Koala is
missing please help don't worry we'll be
我的学前班学生小考拉失踪了 请别担心我们会
请别担心 我们会是
missing please help don't worry we'll be
right
失踪请不要担心 我们会是对的
there it's so
就是这样
hot
那里好热,好热
热热
hot
Miss she when did you find out that
小姐,你什么时候发现
Little Koala is
小姐,你什么时候发现小考拉
小可乐是
Little Koala is
missing I found it out when I was
小考拉失踪了 我发现它,当我在
我想念我发现它,当我在
missing I found it out when I was
counting the children coming off the
当我数着孩子出生时,我发现我失踪了
数着那些刚出生的孩子们
counting the children coming off the
school bus what do I
计数校车下校车的孩子们,
校校车 校车 校车 校车 校车 校车 校车 校车 校车 校车 校车 校车 校车 校车 校校车 校车 校车 校车 校校车 校车 校校车 校校车 校校车 校校车 校校校车 校车 校车
school bus what do I
do I
校校车,我该怎么办?
我做的我
do I
see kids did you see Little Koala taking
我看到孩子了,你有没有看见小考拉
看到孩子了吗? 你看到小考拉吗?
see kids did you see Little Koala taking
the school
看见孩子了吗? 看到小考阿拉 上学了
学校
the school
bus yes I did Little Koala always sleeps
校车,是的,我做了小考拉 总是睡着
巴士是的,我做了小考拉 总是睡着
bus yes I did Little Koala always sleeps
on the
巴士是的,我做了小考拉 总是睡在
会 议 日 程 和 议 程
on the
bus then he might still be on the
然后他可能还在车上
bus where's the bus now it usually goes
然后他可能还在公交车上 公交车现在通常开往哪
公交车现在在哪里? 公交车现在在哪里? 公交车通常开往哪
bus where's the bus now it usually goes
to the school bus parking lot after
公交车现在在哪里? 公交车现在在哪里? 之后通常去学校公交车停车场
之后去学校公交车停车场
to the school bus parking lot after
dropping off all the children do you
学校公交车停车场 之后所有孩子 都下车后,你
所有的小孩都丢弃了,你呢?
dropping off all the children do you
think he's there we'll go look for him
你觉得他在那里吗? 我们去找他
以为他在那里,我们去找他
think he's there we'll go look for him
don't worry there's no case that I can't
以为他在那里,我们去找他 别担心,没有案子我办不到
solve here's the school bus parking lot
这里是校车停车场
the driver missed your y Yak might be
这是学校公交车停车场 司机错过了YYYY的
司机错过了YYYYYY 可能
the driver missed your y Yak might be
around
司机错过了YYYYYAK 可能就在附近
here found him Mr
在这里找到他了 先生
Yak Mr
叶先生
y I'm so sorry I didn't mean
y'm so sorry I'm so sorry 我不是那个意思
it you've got the wrong person here I'm
对不起 我不是故意的 你找错人了
你找错人了
it you've got the wrong person here I'm
Buffalo Mr yak's hair is much longer
你找错人了 我是水牛排 yak先生的头发要长得多
水牛城 yak先生的头发要长得多
Buffalo Mr yak's hair is much longer
than mine sometimes I wonder if he can
水牛先生的头发比我长很多 有时我怀疑他能不能
有时比起我 我怀疑他能不能
than mine sometimes I wonder if he can
actually see when he's
有时我比我自己更想知道 他是否真的能看到
driving well do you know where Mr Yak is
那你知道亚克先生在哪吗?
right
你知不知道亚克先生说的对吗?
右右右右右
right
now no I don't his bus is not
现在不,我不要他的公交车不是
here this is the driver's
这是司机的
schedule this is the logo of the golden
这是金色的徽标
sciss hair salon Mr Yak is probably
这是Yak先生的金剪子发廊的标志
亚克先生大概是
sciss hair salon Mr Yak is probably
getting his haircut there let's
叶先生可能正在理发 我们来
理理理理理发
getting his haircut there let's
go it's so
就是这样
hot where am
热热的地方
I I can't get out help somebody help
我出不来,帮帮忙,帮帮忙
me
我,我,我
it's Little Koala he's stuck inside the
是小科阿拉,他被困在里面
bus oh no he has fainted we need to go
哦,不,他晕倒了,我们得走了
save him right
哦,不,他晕倒了,我们要去救他
now oh no we are stuck we need to run
哦,不,我们被困住了,我们得跑
let's
哦,不,我们被困住了,我们得跑,我们走
go
上去
little
小
KOA call the ambulance
KOA叫救护车
now Sheriff labrador's safety
拉布拉多警长现在的安全
talk
谈 谈 谈
drivers and parents should be careful
说闲聊的司机和家长应该小心
驾驶和驾驶驾驶员及家长应谨慎小心
drivers and parents should be careful
not to leave children alone in the car
家长和司机应注意不要把孩子一个人留在车里。
不让儿童独自留在车里
not to leave children alone in the car
especially in the summer the temperature
特别是在夏季,婴儿不能独自留在车里,温度特别高。
特别是夏天的温度
especially in the summer the temperature
inside the car can get very high so
特别是夏天 车内温度会非常高 所以
车内可以变得非常高 所以
inside the car can get very high so
children's lives might be in
车内可以变得非常高 所以孩子的生活可能在里面
儿童的生命可能与
children's lives might be in
danger also children should always
儿童的生命可能面临危险,儿童也应始终
儿童也始终应:
danger also children should always
remember to get off the bus at the right
儿童在右侧下车时,应时刻记住
记得从右边的巴士上下车
remember to get off the bus at the right
stop if you ever get stuck in a car try
记得在右边的车站下车,如果你被困在汽车里
如果你被困在车里 尝试一下
stop if you ever get stuck in a car try
to go to the driver's seat and unlock
如果你被困在车里 试着去司机的座位 解锁
转到司机的座位 并打开
to go to the driver's seat and unlock
the doors or honk the horn to get
去驾驶员的座位 开门或按喇叭
门或按喇叭
the doors or honk the horn to get
people's
门或按喇叭 得到人们的
人民、人民、人民和
people's
attention please remember these tips
大家注意,请记住这些提示
请注意,请记住这些提示
attention please remember these tips
woof
请注意,请记住这些小费
本字幕由AI大模型生成